invitationbox.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Invitation Box

Last Updated: _April 23, 2016_

This web site is maintained by Phoenix Online, doing business as InvitationBox.com (“InvitationBox”). Here at InvitationBox, we recognize the importance of privacy to our users. We understand that users of our website (the “Website”) are concerned about the personal information (“Personal Information”) they provide us, and how we treat that information. We've developed this Privacy Policy to assure you that we take seriously our responsibility to protect customer information, and to use it only in ways that are consistent with your wishes. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email [privacy@invitationbox.com](mailto:privacy@invitationbox.com).

We may update the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check in occasionally. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by prominently posting a notice on our Website.

**OUR POLICY**  
We do not collect Personal Information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly at InvitationBox. If you are just browsing InvitationBox and learning about our products, we invite you to do so. As a casual, unregistered visitor to our site, we'll recognize your home server (e.g., that your web access is through AOL.com), but not your e-mail address or any other personal or system information.

We sell all of our Products through the mail, so if you order our products it will be necessary for you to provide Personal Information. This will include your name, address, phone number and, if you place an order online, credit card information. Any information you provide is downloaded off of the web server to a secure system and is maintained there.

**OUR CUSTOMER LIST**  
When you purchase items from our online catalog, you can opt to have your name added to our Customer List. We will not share your email address with any third parties at any time. If you prefer not to receive mailings from us, please advise us by using the mail, phone or e-mail address provided above. Please include your name and address if you are contacting us by mail or e-mail. We will ensure that your name is removed from the list.

**CONTACTS FROM US**  
We maintain a number of e-mail mailboxes in an effort to support our online customers as effectively as we do on the phone or through the mail. We read every e-mail that we receive and do our best to respond within 48 hours, if a response is required. We save a very limited number of e-mail messages, but only until the issue is resolved. We do not record email addresses, unless you have voluntarily provided it to us in your online customer service registration.

If you did provide us with your e-mail address, we may notify you from time to time about InvitationBox products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive these e-mail notifications, please follow the "Opt-out" instructions included with the e-mail or contact us at [privacy@invitationbox.com](mailto:privacy@invitationbox.com).

**COOKIES**  
Like most companies, we use "cookies" (small pieces of information stored on your computer) on certain parts of our web site. The cookie allows us to manage your session. This is necessary to ensure that we keep your order together while you browse through the catalog and select items for purchase. We do not use the cookie to collect any type of personal information, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer.

**SECURITY ONLINE**  
Most of our forms, especially when ordering a product or using online customer service, use secure pages to insure that the information sent between your computer and our system is secure. This is especially true if we are asking you for payment information.

We use the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption method on all secure submissions. This method is generally accepted to insure that the transmission of Personal Information, such as account numbers and credit card information is secure. The most common browsers, Firefox and Internet Explorer, make it very obvious when information is being passed in a secure manner by showing either a completed key or a closed lock on the screen.

**Contacting InvitationBox  
**You can reach us 24 hours a day, 7 days a week by sending email to [customerservice@invitationbox.com](mailto:customerservice@invitationbox.com). If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: InvitationBox, 5512 Caterpillar Drive, Apex, North Carolina 27539. We will be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns. ****

**_Notice to California Residents._  
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by InvitationBox and its related companies to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this privacy policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@invitationbox.com](mailto:privacy@invitationbox.com) or write us: **

**InvitationBox  
5512 Caterpillar Drive  
Apex, North Carolina, 27539**
